{
    "id": "b720a2e5f7ce4ad7ba4d2bfcdd5b3f2b",
    "title": "Change statement into questions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "6aba07d866b94fe1ada05bcd11b648ea",
            "title": "Formation Of Questions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": ".................................... my mother make delicious cakes?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Has",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. my sister work at a bank?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... he spend a lot of time working on his computer?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Has",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. my father go to office by car?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... the children practise the piano every morning?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Have",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... our team play well yesterday?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................... I meet your dad yesterday?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. he want to go abroad?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Do",
                        "Does",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ Susie sing well?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... Maya buy a new car last week?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Does",
                        "Do",
                        "Did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}